Aida Maisonet

3 Short Street
2nd floor
New Britain, CT 06051
8607705048
Ammaisonet@hotmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To obtain a position at a medical office where I can practice all the medical skills I have learned on my training at Lincoln Technical Institute. My skills include but are not limited to phlebotomy, obtaining vital signs, scheduling patients, filling, and computer skills.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Administrative: telephone techniques, computer filing, Knowledge of computer program Microsoft Word, More than seven years experience of outstanding customer service, making audits on registers, and filing employee information such as attendance and quality of work.

EDUCATION

Lincoln Technical Institute, New Britain, CT
Medical Assistant Program Diploma – April, 2010
GPA: 3.2 Studies included: Anatomy & Physiology, Medical Terminology, Medical Laboratory Skills,
Pharmacology, Insurance Coding & Billing, Law & Ethics, Business English, Typing & Transcription.CPR
certified

EMPLOYMENT

Stop and Shop Newington, CT

March 2008- June 2009

Head cashier, answering phones, resolving customer's problems, resolving any issues cashiers have, scheduling, audits on registers and cashiers, Customer service.

Stop and Shop April 2007- December 2007 Newington, CT

Head cashier, answering phones, resolving customer's problems, resolving any issues cashiers have, scheduling, audits on registers and cashiers, Customer service.

Smiles Entertainment Center April 2002- December 2005 Milford, CT

Customer service, Party hostess, scheduling, supervise employees, scheduling parties, answering phones and promoting their services.

Externship

St.Francis campus 1000 Aslyum street, Hartford, CT

March 28,2011 to current

Medical Assistant

My responsibilities as an extern in the Rheumatology office located at St.Francis hospital are to schedule appointments for patients, filling charts, taking messages for the physicians, checking patients in and out, faxing patient 's prescriptions to pharmacies, taking patient 's vital signs, and recording it in charts. I am currently at my externship and i am learning something new everyday.